Ayinde Elizabeth Ayomide

09059972694| ayindeayomide7@gmail.com |16,Jire Aransi Close,Ojoo 11th August,2022.

Jason Hreha

CEO,Persona Worldwide,US

Dear Mr. Hreha,

I am excited to be applying for the role of Virtual Executive Assistant, which I saw was recently posted on LinkedIn.I am especially thrilled about this position because administrative tasks and projects are one of my favorite tasks and I excel at it.

I am incredibly analytical and creative too and these skills would be greatly and efficiently put to use in this role. I also do well in gathering research, use of spreadsheets, events and meetings planning and drafting of emails.

In line with the job description, it appears I am extremely fit for this position. I am fluent in English Language, I am skilled in the use of apps and technology and I am able to commit myself fully to work without being overwhelmed.

A great endurance ability to persevere and willingness to work hard are abilities I possess including intellectual curiosity and a great resourcefulness skill which I would love to put to use in this organization. I have been able to put them to practice while working as a little cousin assistant for my cousin some time ago. I am sure that this experience will also help me pick up new skills and bring more excellent feedback for the company.

My track record of success in anything I find myself doing goes with my philosophy that, "anything worth doing, is worth doing well". I am a great team player too.

I sincerely hope I am opportune to speak further so I can share more about myself, my unique strengths and my enthusiasm for this role.

Thank you so much for your time and consideration.

Best regards, Ayinde Elizabeth Ayomide

AYINDE ELIZABETH

Nigerian | 16, Jire Aransi Close | +2349059972694 ayindeayomide7@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayindeayomide

SUMMARY

- Enthusiastic team player.
- Excels in providing exceptional service to clients.
- Analyzed and maintained various accounting activities.

EDUCATION

University of Ibadan – Ibadan, Nigeria

June 2019– November 2024

BA, European Studies

ALX Africa - Virtual Assistant Program

July 2022 - present

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Representative - Olajide Stores

May 2017 - December 2018

- Prepared monthly and weekly reports.
- Gave sales presentations to clients.
- Collected bills and Managed accounts.

Teacher - Olubunmi Divine College

January 2018 - September 2018

- Worked closely with other teachers to ensure all avenues of the curriculum are met and delivered lessons to the students.
- Encouraged students to develop interest in language learning.
- Established and maintained rapport with other staffs, students

VOLUNTEER ACTIVITIES

Personal Assistant - To my Cousin

December 2018 - May 2019

- Planned and Organized schedule.
- Arranged meetings and appointments.
- Efficiently administered a variety of accounting activities.

SKILLS

Coding skills

Translating skill

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JAVASCRIPT

INTERESTS

Learning Languages Technology Data Analysis

LANGUAGES

Yoruba - Native

English - Expert

French - Conversational

Russian - Intermediate